[
  {
    "id": "01",
    "question": "What is Java?",
    "answer": "Java is a high-level, class-based, oject-oiriented programming language.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "essential",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "02",
    "question": "In Java, all functions are associated with what?",
    "answer": "In Java, all functions are associated with classes.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "InDepth",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "03",
    "question": "Since all functions in Java are associated with classes, what are all functions called?",
    "answer": "In Java all functions are methods.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "04",
    "question": "In Java, where must all code (except import statements) be written?",
    "answer": "In Java, all code (except import statements) must be written inside a class.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "05",
    "question": "In Java, where must all code (except import statements) be written?",
    "answer": "In Java, all executable code (except import statements) must be written inside a method.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "06",
    "question": "Java is a strongly-typed language. What does this mean?",
    "answer": "Java being a sytongly-typed language means the type of a variable must be declared when said variable is created.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "07",
    "question": "In Java, what is the naming convention for all variables that aren't constants?",
    "answer": "In Java, all variables except constants are camelCased.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "08",
    "question": "What method do all Java applications need?",
    "answer": "All Java applications need a main method.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "09",
    "question": "In Java, which method is the first to be ran in an application?",
    "answer": "In Java, the first method to be ran is the main method.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "Which method is the entry point into a Java application?",
    "answer": "In Java, the main method is the entry point into an application.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "question": "In Java, all functions are associated with what?",
    "answer": "In Java, all functions are associated with classes.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "InDepth",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "question": "Since all functions in Java are associated with classes, what are all functions called?",
    "answer": "In Java all functions are methods.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "question": "In Java, where must all code (except import statements) be written?",
    "answer": "In Java, all code (except import statements) must be written inside a class.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "question": "In Java, where must all executable code (except import statements) be written?",
    "answer": "In Java, all executable code (except import statements) must be written inside a method.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "question": "Java is a strongly-typed language. What does this mean?",
    "answer": "Java being a sytongly-typed language means the type of a variable must be declared when said variable is created.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "question": "In Java, what is the naming convention for all variables that aren't constants?",
    "answer": "In Java, all variables except constants are camelCased.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "question": "What method do all Java applications need?",
    "answer": "All Java applications need a main method.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "question": "In Java, which method is the first to be ran in an application?",
    "answer": "In Java, the first method to be ran is the main method.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "question": "Which method is the entry point into a Java application?",
    "answer": "In Java, the main method is the entry point into an application.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "fundamentals",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "question": "What are the primitive data types in Java?",
    "answer": "In Java, the primitive data types are: byte, short, int, long, float, double, boolean, char.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "21",
    "question": "What are the composite data types in Java?",
    "answer": "In Java, the composite data types are: Strings, Arrays, Objects, Classes, Interfaces.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "22",
    "question": "What are the Non-Primitive data types in Java?",
    "answer": "In Java, the composite data types are: Strings, Arrays, Objects, Classes, Interfaces.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "23",
    "question": "What does the byte data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type byte stores whole numbers from -128 to 127.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "24",
    "question": "What does the short data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type short stores whole numbers from -32,768 to 32,767.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-Types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "25",
    "question": "What does the int data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type stores whole numbers from -2,147,483,648 to 2,147,483,647.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "26",
    "question": "What does the long data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type stores numbers from -9,223,372,036,854,775,808 to 9,223,372,036,854,775,807.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "27",
    "question": "What does the float data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type  float stores fractional numbers. Sufficient for storing 6 to 7.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "28",
    "question": "What does the double data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type double stores fractional numbers. Sufficient for storing 15 decimal digits.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "29",
    "question": "What does the boolean data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type boolean stores true or false values.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "30",
    "question": "What does the char data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type char stores a single character/letter or ASCII values.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "31",
    "question": "What two groups are the primitive number types divided into?",
    "answer": "Integer types and Floating point types.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "32",
    "question": "What do the integer types store?",
    "answer": "The integer types stores whole numbers, positive or negative without decimals.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "33",
    "question": "What do the flopating point types store?",
    "answer": "Numbers with a fractional part, containing one or more decimals.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "34",
    "question": "What are the most used number types in Java?",
    "answer": "The most used are int (for whole numbers) and double (for floating point numbers).",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "35",
    "question": "What does the long data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type stores numbers from -9,223,372,036,854,775,808 to 9,223,372,036,854,775,807.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "36",
    "question": "What does the long data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type stores numbers from -9,223,372,036,854,775,808 to 9,223,372,036,854,775,807.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "37",
    "question": "What does the long data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type stores numbers from -9,223,372,036,854,775,808 to 9,223,372,036,854,775,807.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "38",
    "question": "What does the long data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type stores numbers from -9,223,372,036,854,775,808 to 9,223,372,036,854,775,807.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "39",
    "question": "What does the long data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type stores numbers from -9,223,372,036,854,775,808 to 9,223,372,036,854,775,807.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  },
  {
    "id": "40",
    "question": "What does the long data type store?",
    "answer": "The primitive data type stores numbers from -9,223,372,036,854,775,808 to 9,223,372,036,854,775,807.",
    "Bonus": "",
    "urgency": "critical",
    "typeOfQuestion": "shortAnswer",
    "render": "static",
    "direction": "forward",
    "topic": "languages",
    "subTopic1": "Java",
    "subTopic2": "Data-types",
    "chapter": "01",
    "source": "Ironhack"
  }
]
